randy rebucas

Cavite, Calabarzon, Philippines

rebucasrandy1986@gmail.com

09179157515

linkedin.com/in/randy-rebucas-1a896943

Summary

Over years of experience of doing things such as web development, I just discover things which are best, not just knowing new things, new discoveries, and new knowledge but also knowing things on how to handle person opinion and being optimistic in all manners.

Experience

Mobile Engineer

TriSeed Software, Inc.

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023 (10 months)

- Structure app for super app and used react native and reack.js
- Implement third party application using API's
- Developed Back Office to manage all dynamic data's

nti Java Developer

NTI

Jun 2022 - Feb 2023 (9 months)

- Fix bugs from frontend Angular App.
- Implement new functionalities using Angular and Springboot.
- Restructure Components to make it reusable.

Mid Tier Developer

Acquire BPO

Jun 2021 - Nov 2022 (1 year 6 months)

- Developed Magento Extentions.
- Customized Design and Layouts.
- Implement API's

🥏 Senior Software Engineer

Cloudstaff

Sep 2017 - May 2021 (3 years 9 months)

- Developed Extentions for Magento 1.
- Implement UI/UX design to magento web page layout.
- Fix Bugs/Errors.

фивт Magento Developer

UBT Australia and New Zealand

Sep 2017 - May 2021 (3 years 9 months)

- Developed Extentions for Magento 1.

- Implement UI/UX design to magento web page layout.
- Fix Bugs/Errors.

Magento Developer

optiBPO

Sep 2017 - May 2021 (3 years 9 months)

- Developed Extentions for Magento 1.
- Implement UI/UX design to magento web page layout.
- Fix Bugs/Errors.

Senior Web Developer

4D Systems

Dec 2016 - Jul 2017 (8 months)

- Developed Extentions for Magento 1.
- Implement UI/UX design to magento web page layout.
- Fix Bugs/Errors.
- Restructure layout to make it responsive.

Web Developer

Comet Digital Media

Apr 2013 - Feb 2014 (11 months)

- Developed WP plugins.
- Customization of Layout and Design.
- Create custom scripts.
- Fix bugs/errors.

Education

Visayas State University Main Campus - Baybay City, Leyte

Bachelor's degree, AgreBusiness 2008 - 2011

Licenses & Certifications

Angular and Nodejs - The MEAN Stack guide - Udemy UC-GO6DLEI1

Angular 8 (formerly angular 2) - Udemy

UC-Q9LG5WQE

- lonic 4 Build iOS, Android & Web Apps with Ionic & Angular Udemy UC-B231TXTI
- Build and Deploy Your First Decentralized App with Ethereum Udemy

Advance jQuery - Udemy

UC-f7ff7e7c-b1c0-4f9d-ab2e-36f48426da01

React Native - Tha Practical Guide [2023] - Udemy

UC-c60c0c8e-9681-4cb8-a576-8629e8fe3b3a

Skills

Full-Stack Development • TypeScript • Laravel • AngularJS • PHP • Web Development • CodeIgniter • jQuery • phpMyAdmin • MySQL